-
Speaker 1: Based on what I've seen, Chuck E. Cheese is the last place where adults should
Speaker 2: be. - A woman got stuck inside a money grabbing machine at a Chuck E. Cheese restaurant in Burbank.
-
Speaker 3: A still unidentified woman inside the Snow Day game console on her knees, her
Speaker 4: right hand stuck in a hole. Burbank firefighters took 22 minutes to free her.
- Look, you
Speaker 1: can't just call the fire department to save this imbecile, okay?
Speaker 1: This is Chuck E. Cheese. You have to win her. Okay? Fair
Speaker 5: and square. But hey, maybe I'm being too hard on this dumbass woman, okay? I'm sure this happens all the time. Snow
Speaker 3: Day is manufactured by a company called Coastal Amusements, said company president Michael Dean. There are hundreds of these games and Chuck E. Cheese's throughout the country, and we've never seen something like this happen before. Wow,
this is
Speaker 1: really exciting. I mean, she found a completely undiscovered way to be an idiot. Give
her a
Speaker 1: Nobel Prize, preferably one with no sharp edges.